Guide to the Records of the Vice President and Deputy Chancellor and Senior Vice President, Debra James 1980-2000 RG.6.1.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Vice President Gore Visit, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - State of the University Dinner, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Walter Mosely, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Eleanor Korman Reception, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Knicks Reception, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - John Hartford Foundation Dinner, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Halloween, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - City Club Luncheon, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Wendy Wasserstein, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Luncheon Honoring Tom Blum's Daughter, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Tiro A. Segno Foundation Ball, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Reception for New Medical Dean--Robert Glickman, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Vernon Dedication, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Lunch with Sylvia Hassenfeld, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Zerilli-Marimo Prize for Italian Fiction, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Conversations at Washington Square with Danny Glover, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Vice President Luncheon (C-Team), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Celebration of CSC (CSPS) Name Change, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Induction Dinner for Law School Trustees, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Heights Overlook Dedication, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Varsity Club Hall of Fame Dinner, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Chaminade Luncheon, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - S.A. Delegate Breakfast, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Lewis Rudin Scholars Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - President Jose Jamie Rivera (Afternoon Tea), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - GSAS Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Remarks by Jules A. Martin NYU Welcome Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Guestlist for Jules Martin Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Admissions Office Thank You Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Amsterdam Breakfast, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Goldberg Dedication and Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Guestlist, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Emails, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Faxes, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Annette Weiner, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Vice President/Deputy Chancellor Forms, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Lewis Rudin Scholars Reception, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Sunday at the Square, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Kaufman Retirement Dinner, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Protection Awards, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Caldero Meeting, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - TSOA Commencement Salute Platform Party Program Scripts, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226344 5
  - Todd Cohen Commencement Speaker, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - VP Gore's Speech Writers, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Meeting, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Commencement 1998 Issues for Senior Vice President Meeting (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Community Service, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Creative Arts Team, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Culinary Institute of America, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Day Care Issues--GA/TA, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Department of French--Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - DePaul University, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Design and Stage, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Development Manual, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dick Koppenaal, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - District Learning, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Distinguished Administrator Awards, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Distinguished Administrator Awards, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Distinguished Teaching Award Meeting, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Diversity Learning, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Ellie Campbell, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Economist, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - EEO, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Ellis Island Medals of Honor, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Executive Coaching, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee of the Board, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee of the Students Senators Council, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Colloquia, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Academic Calendar, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226345 2
  - ACF, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Administration/Staff Retreat, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Afro-American Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Afro-American Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - La Pietra--Jazz Conference, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Audiovisual Problems, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Allen Hevesi, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Trustee Breakfast, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - AMA, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - AMA (binder), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AMC End of Year Dinner, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AMC Tuition Meeting, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - AMC Dinner, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - AMC, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Alvin Kassan, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Anthropology, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Archivist, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Ari Gutman, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - BCCC - The Black Community Crusade for Children, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bell Atlantic, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Bennett College, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Goldfeld, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Bridal Registry, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Brigadoon, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Capetown, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Caring Community, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Cartier, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Curriculum Development Challenge Fund, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Center for French Civilization and Culture, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Chaminade University, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Childcare, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Childcare Center, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Christie's, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Christmas Cards, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Christmas Luncheon--Invitation, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Christmas Luncheon--Grab Bag, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Christmas Luncheon--Menu, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Christmas Luncheon--Emails, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Christmas Luncheon--Faxes, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Christmas Luncheon--Guest Lists, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Christmas Luncheon--RSVP Lists, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Claire Fagin, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - FRN Presidents Dinner--Dr. Vartan Gregorian, President Carnegie Corp, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226346 0
  - FRN Presidents Dinner--Deborah's Speech, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - FRN Presidents Dinner--FRN Talking Points, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - FRN Annual Liason Officers Meeting, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - FRN Biannual Meeting of Liason Officers, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - FRN Summer Program, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Gerald A. Heeger, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Glenn Langden, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Gloria King Allen, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Grad Alleys, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Grad Alleys, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Gard Alley Planning Guide, 19981999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - GSAS, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Greenwich House Preschool, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - GSAS Search, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Healthy Talk, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Heidrick and Struggles, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - High Hopes, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hotel/Travel Brochures, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Humanities Council, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Information Technology, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226347 8
  - Institute on College Student Values, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - International Corridor, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - International Recruiting, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - International Program, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - International Programs (Harvey's Office), undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - International Recruiting, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - International Students and Scholars, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Leonard Stern Capital Investment Program, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Italian Database--Acton Scholars, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Italian Database--GEI, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Italian Database--Italian Dept, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Italian Database--Casa Italiana Advisory Board, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Italian Database--Acton Society Members, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Italian Database, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Italian Database for December Events--Distribution List, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Italian Database for December Events--Emails, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Italian Database for December Events--Faxes, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Italian Database for December Events--Invitation, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Italian Database for December Events--Telephone Numbers, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Italian Database for December Events--RSVP List, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Italian Progressive Clubs, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Italy, Greece Trip, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - John F. Caruso, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Johns Hopkins, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - John Johnson, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Joseph A. Fonti, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Junior Staff, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Kaplan Educational Center, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Karen Greenburg, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - King Hussein I, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Krispy Kreme, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Ladies Retreat, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Laura Mason, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Leadership Alliance, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Learning Course Development, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Lee Frissell, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Legal Correspondence, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Letters--Dec, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Letters--Nov, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Letters--Oct, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Letters--Sept, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Library Dean Search--Larry Alfred, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Library Dean Search--Carol Ann Mandel, undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Library Dean Search--Carol Ann Mandel, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Literary Week, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - L.L. Bean, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Lobbyist, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Loretta Glucksman, undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Loyola High Schools, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Maya Lin Event--Meeting, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Mexico City Trip, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Michael Mallon Lunch, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Paolo Curcio--Conti, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Peter Lennie, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Pete Yon-Sik Kang, undated (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Phil Fermanski, undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Phil Fermanski, undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Prof. Jane Ashdown, undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Renee Blake, undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Richard Koppanal, undated (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Sheila Bolar, undated (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Stephanie Bell Rose, undated (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Suada Kapic, undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Tom Bishop, undated (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Trisha's Itinerary to Italy, undated (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Trish McNicholas, undated (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Trish's Travel Itinerary to Prague, undated (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - International Binder (La Pietra), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226348 6
  - Rector's Conferences, 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Americorps Direct Renewal Application, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Robert F. Wagner School of Public Service- Confidential For Search Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - School Year Planner, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226349 4
  - School Year Planner, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - School Year Planner, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - School Year Planner, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - School Year Planner, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - School Year Planner, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - School Year Planner, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - School Year Planner, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - School Year Planner, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - School Year Planner, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - School Year Planner, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - School Year Planner, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - School Year Planner, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - School Year Planner, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - School Year Planner, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - School Year Planner, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - School Year Planner, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - School Year Planner, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - School Year Planner, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - School Year Planner, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - School Year Planner, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - School Year Planner, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - School Year Planner, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - General Photos of Installation, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Assorted Events (Photos), undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226351 0
  - Vice President and Deputy Chancellor Debra James, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Vice President and Deputy Chancellor Debra James, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Kirsten Alvanson, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226352 8
  - Architectural Materials, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Stergios Bekas, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Morris Bergreen Mtg., 1998 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Bishop, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Paolo Blasi, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Board of Regents, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Bottom Line, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Building Plans, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - C3 Restaurant and Lounge, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Charters and Bylaws, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Hugo Chavez, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - City Harvest, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Libby Egnor, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Resource Network (FRN), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Files, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Foodworks, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Law School Event, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Dan Quilty Foundation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Search Letters, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Selection Committee for Community Service, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Service Project Grant, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Allen Sessoms, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - David Sgarlata, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Marguerite Sharkey, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Sigmund Shen, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Arthur T. Shorin, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Fred Siff, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Sharon Slotnick, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - General Solano, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Spain, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Cynthia Neal Spence, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Student Commencement Screening, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - TFAC, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - PR Firm/France, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226353 6
  - University Hall Plaque Dedication, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Induction Dinner for Law School Trustees, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Briefing for Welcome Back Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - New Faculty Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sharon Slotnick, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Dinner in Honor of Gerald Heeger, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Protection Awards Ceremony, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rob Manuel and Wilmara Henriquez Upcoming Nuptials, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Hospital Industry Investment Conference Breakfast, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Susan D. Hibbard Scholarship Ceremony, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Arte's, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Matilda Cuomo Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Kriser Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - ABFAS Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Reception for Eleanore Korman's Retirement, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - 25 Year Service Awards Breakfast, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Service Recognition Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - NYU Community Fund Awards, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - ABFAS Luncheon and Award Ceremony, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Council Annual Dinner, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Farewell Reception for Dean Rochell, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Admissions Office Thank You Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Distinguished Administrator Awards Dinner, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - CHUBB-NYU Scholarship/Internship Program Recognition Breakfast, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Janet and Barry's Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Student Senator Year End Dinner, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - OASIS 10th Anniversary Awards Celebration, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Give A Violet Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - MLK Senior Reception for the 9th Graduating Class, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Dedication of the Jewel Zelensky Lounge, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Welcome Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Kriser Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Founder's Day Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Student Athlete Academic Achievement Awards, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - New Trustee Dinner, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - National Scholarship, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Rectors "Thank You" Reception, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Special Tribute Honoring Laurence A. Tisch, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - University Hall Dedication, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Dinner Honoring Wole Soyinka, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - League of World Universities 5th Conference, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Vernon Dedication Dinner, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - C-Team Orientation, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Sir Harold Acton Event, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Luncheon in honor of Dr. Wilmot James, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - FAS Luncheon Meeting, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Reception in Honor of Carol Mandel, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Welcome Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - 3rd Annual Christmas Grab-Bag, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Christmas Luncheon, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Young Alumni Event, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - All-University Holiday Sing, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Strategies for Hiring Underrepresented Faculty, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Conversations at Washington Square with Alan G. Hevesi, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Andrea Scavetta Dinner, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Guidance Counselor Reception, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Loews Corporation, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Claire Fagan Reception, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Morning at Washington Square, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - 29 WSW Penthouse, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227217 2
  - Hayden Hall Penthouse, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hayden Hall Penthouse, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Child Care Center: Visits, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Child Care: Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Child Care Subcommittee, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Housing Task Force Meetings, 19891990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Planning Committee, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Enhancing the Role of the University in the Urban Setting, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Urban Setting Subcommittee: Volunteers & Funding Programs, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Chancellor's Service Awards, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Vice President for Institutional Facilities Search, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Evaluation of the Office of Dean Rochell (Libraries), undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Non-Faculty Review, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Dean's Reviews, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Dean Rochelle's Review (Libraries), May 1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Deans' Evaluations: General File, 19771980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Stedman/Baruch Transition Materials, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226362 7
  - GAL Dean Herbert London, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Review London (Gallatin), 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - GSAS Dean Search, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Evaluation: Daniel E. Griffiths (SEHNAP), undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Review: Dean Robert Burnham (SEHNAP), 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - SCE Dean's Review, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ann Marcus/Robert Burnham Announcement Materials, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - SEHNAP Deanship, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Trustee Inquiries, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Student Problems, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Trustee Inquiries, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Janice Iovino Students, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Debra James Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rhodes Scholarships, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Janice Iovino Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Administration Position Requests, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Liaison Officer, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226354 4
  - Manhattan, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Stan Martin, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Mazzola, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Marylin McMillian, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Menu, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Tom Mitchell, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dianne Modestini, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Marhruoo Moshrir, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Walter Mosely, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Walter Mosely, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Mystical Mouthfuls, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Janer Neipris, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Marjorie P. Felcher Newman, MD, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - NYU/Charles University Exchange Program, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--September, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--August, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--July, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--June, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--May, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--April, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--March, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--February, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - L. Jay O. Letters--January, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Organized Executive, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Evelynne Patterson, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Petty Cash, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Prague, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Prentice Hall, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Presidential Citations, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Prestigious Scholarship, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Rectors Visit, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Rectors Visit, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Rectors Follow-Up Meeting, undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - League of World Nations Meeting, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Rectors Flag Meeting, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - European Rectors Planning Meeting, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Rectors Tele-Conference, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Rectors Tele-Conference Meeting, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Rectors Conference, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Young Alumni Holiday Party, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - League of World Universities 5th Conference, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226355 1
  - Millbank House, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - President's Holiday Parties, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - President's Holiday Parties, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Provincetown, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Results of Meeting, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Rhodes Scholar, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ying Wu, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Martin Francis Kindl--Rhodes Scholar, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Charles Knutson, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)